Dorothy C. Miller
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Dorothy C. Miller papers
circa 1912-1992, bulk 1959-1984
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Miller, Dorothy Canning
24.7 linear feet
The papers of contemporary art curator, historian, and consultant Dorothy C. Miller measure 24.7 linear feet and date from circa 1912-1992, with the bulk of the material dating from 1959 to 1984. The papers primarily concern Miller's career after retiring from the Museum of Modern Art in New York City. Found are scattered biographical materials, extensive correspondence and subject files, and project files for her art advisory and committee work for the Rockefeller family, Rockefeller University, Chase Manhattan Bank, the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, the World Trade Center, and other miscellaneous corporate and private clients. Miller's work as a trustee and committee member of various public and private boards and commissions is also represented here. Additionally, the papers contain Miller's research files on Edward Hicks and folk art, and a small number of files of her husband Holger Cahill about his work as Director of the Federal Art Project. There is a scattered documentation of Miller's early curatorial work with Holger Cahill on the First Municipal Art Exhibition (1934) held at the RCA Building in Rockefeller Center. Also found is Dorothy Miller's collection of artists' Christmas cards and photographs of Miller and others.
Provenance
The collection was donated by Dorothy C. Miller via Wendy Jeffers between 1986 and 1997, and Reid White, Executor of Miller's estate, in 2004.
Restrictions on Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment.
Related Material
The Archives of American Art holds two oral history interviews with Dorothy C. Miller. The first was conducted by Paul Cummings between May 26, 1970 and September 28, 1971, and details Miller's life from childhood up to, and including, her years at the Museum of Modern Art. The second was conducted by Avis Berman on May 14, 1981 and covers Miller's relationships with Mark Rothko and Clyfford Still. Also found among the holdings of the Archives are the papers of Holger Cahill, Dorothy Miller's husband and colleague.
The Museum of Modern Art Achives holds Dorothy Miller's papers related to her curatorial work at the museum.
Biographical Note
Dorothy Canning Miller (1904-2003) worked in New York City as a highly influential curator of contemporary art and was the first curator of the Museum of Modern Art. Later, she worked as as an art advisor and consultant to Nelson A. Rockefeller, the Rockefeller family, Rockefeller University, Chase Manhattan Bank, and the Port Authority of and New Jersey. Dorothy Miller was also married to Holger Cahill, director of the WPA Federal Art Project.
Dorothy C. Miller was born in Hopedale, Massachusetts in 1904 and received her Bachelor of Arts from Smith College in 1925. She was first introduced to modern art through classes at the Newark Museum taught by John Cotton Dana and Holger Cahill. Miller joined the curatorial staff of the Newark Museum in 1926. The museum was one of the first to organize exhibitions of American folk art, American Primitives (1930-1931) and American Folk Sculpture (1931-1932). Miller worked with Cahill and others on the exhibition and developed a life-long interest in folk art.
After four years at the Newark Museum, Miller moved to New York city, hoping to get involved with the newly opened Museum of Modern Art (MOMA), and, likely, to be with Holger Cahill, with whom she lived with on 8th Street prior to their marriage in 1938. Between 1930 and 1932 she took odd jobs and worked with Mrs. Henry Lang cataloging, researching and installing Lang's collection of Native American art Lang donated to the Montclair Art Museum. At the same time, Holger Cahill was serving as Acting Director of the Museum of Modern Art during an absence of Director Alfred H. Barr. In 1932, Cahill asked Miller to assist him with curating the American Painting and Sculpture, 1862-1932 exhibition at MOMA, and together they also curated the First Municipal Art Exhibition, 1934 at the Rockefeller Center.
In 1934, Barr hired Miller as his assistant and one year later appointed her as MOMA's first curator. Miller spent the next 35 years organizing many of this country's most important exhibitions of contemporary art and building personal relationships with new artists and photographers, as well as the collections of MOMA. Some of her more important shows included New Horizons in American Art, 1936; Calder: 19 Gifts from the Artists, 1967; and Twentieth Century Art from the Nelson Aldrich Rockefeller Collection, 1969. As a curator, Miller enjoyed close friendships with contemporary artists of all ages, such as AlCopley, Alexander Calder, Chryssa, Arshile Gorky, Will Horwitt, Loren MacIver, and Louise Nevelson, among many others. Miller retired from MOMA in 1969 but continued to have an influential career as art consultant and advisor.
Dorothy Miller assisted and advised Nelson A. Rockefeller in building his vast personal collection of modern art, much of which ended up in the permanent collection of the Museum of Modern Art. Just prior to her retirement, Miller organized a large exhibition of Rockefeller's collection. The exhibition catalog written by Miller was the basis for the book she worked on following Rockefeller's death in 1979, ultimately published as The Nelson A. Rockefeller Collection: Masterpieces of Modern Art. In the preface, Rockefeller credited Miller with being one of the four people to whom he was indebted "for the understanding and endless joy I have found in the collecting of modern art in all forms."
Miller also served as the primary art consultant for projects to furnish federal spaces, including Henry Kissinger's State Department office suite, and the official Vice-Presidential residence at the Admiral's House in Washington D.C.
In 1959 Miller was invited to join the art collection committee of the Chase Manhattan Bank and served on the committee until the mid-1980s, contributing her expertise to the development of one of this country's oldest and largest corporate collections of modern and contemporary art. She was also hired as an art advisor to First National City Bank, now Citibank.
Miller was also an advisor to other members of the Rockefeller family, including David Rockefeller, and assisted with developing the art collections of Rockefeller Institute/University. From 1960 through the late 1980s Miller was a member of the art committee for the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey (PANJY) and was responsible for selecting much of the artwork for the World Trade Center in the 1970s. She served on numerous boards, committees, and commissions, including the Hancock Shaker Village, the Smithsonian Institution's Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, the Empire State Plaza in Albany, and the Smith College Museum of Art. She also became a member of the Mark Rothko Foundation Board of Directors after the litigation following Rothko's death between Rothko's executors and his daughter.
In the mid-1970s Miller assisted the Whitney Museum of American with planning an exhibition and supporting catalog of the work of folk artist Edward Hicks. Although the exhibition and catalog were only partially realized in 1980, Miller and Eleanore Price Mather compiled and published a book on Hicks, Edward Hicks: His Peaceable Kingdoms and Other Paintings, published in 1983.
In 1982-1983 Miller received the Art Dealers Association Special Award, an honorary degree from Williams College, and the Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture governor's award. In 1984 she was named honorary trustee of the Museum of Modern Art. In 1985 the Smith College Museum of Art honored her important contributions to museum connoisseurship with the exhibition Dorothy C. Miller: With An Eye to American Art.
Dorothy Miller died in 2003 at the age of 99 at her home in Greenwich Village in New York City.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of contemporary art curator, historian, and consultant Dorothy C. Miller measure 24.7 linear feet and date from circa 1912-1992, with the bulk of the material dating from 1959 to 1984. The papers primarily concern Miller's career after retiring from the Museum of Modern Art in New York City. Found are scattered biographical materials, extensive correspondence and subject files, and project files for her art advisory and committee work for the Rockefeller family, Rockefeller University, Chase Manhattan Bank, the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, the World Trade Center, and other miscellaneous corporate and private clients. Files documenting Miller's published catalog Masterpieces of Modern Art, The Nelson A. Rockefeller Collection are also found. Miller's work as a trustee and committee member of various public and private boards and commissions is also represented here. Additionally, the papers contain Miller's research files on Edward Hicks and folk art, and a small number of files of her husband Holger Cahill about his work as Director of the Federal Art Project. There is a scattered documentation of Miller's early curatorial work with Holger Cahill on the First Municipal Art Exhibition (1934) held at the RCA Building in Rockefeller Center. Also found are Dorothy Miller's collection of artists' Christmas cards and photographs of Miller and others.
Scattered biographical material mostly concerns Miller's education at Smith College and awards and honorary degrees that she received. Extensive correspondence and subject files document her professional and personal relationships with family, friends, colleagues, museums, art dealers and artists, as well as her research interests. Individual files may contain a mix of correspondence with, as well as about, the person or subject, compiled research documents, printed materials, and scattered photographs. Files are found for Lewin Alcopley, Alfred Barr, Betty Parsons Gallery, Cahill family members, Lee Bontecou, James Byars, Holger Cahill, Alexander Calder, Christo, Chryssa, Calvert Coggeshall, John Canaday, Maryette Charlton, Stuart Davis, Jay DeFeo, Lorser Feitelson, Arshile Gorky, Peggy Guggenheim, Grace Hartigan, Will Horwitt, Jasper Johns, Julien Levy, Pierre Matisse, Louise Nevelson, Barnett Newman, Isamu Nauchi, Georgia O'Keefe, Pablo Picasso, Robert Rauschenberg, Ad Reinhardt, Kay Sage, Charles Sheeler, Hedda Sterne, travel, Clyfford Still, William Scharf, among many others.
Detailed records of Miller's art advisory work for the Rockefeller family include correspondence with Nelson A. Rockefeller and David Rockefeller about building their personal collections of contemporary and folk art, meeting notes and minutes, research notes and writings, and printed materials. The largest group of records concerns the writing and publication of Masterpieces of Modern Art, The Nelson A. Rockefeller Collection. Miller's curatorial work for David Rockefeller and the Rockefeller University's Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Hall art collection is documented in Series 4 through curatorial files, correspondence, printed materials, photographs and slides, artists files, and design records.
Series 5 contains files relating to Miller's work as art consultant to the Chase Manhattan Bank and the building of the corporation's extensive collection of contemporary art. There is a draft of Miller's text for the bank's published catalog, Art At Work: Chase Manhattan Bank Collection. A smaller set of records is found in Series 6 documenting Miller's work on the Art Committee of the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, including files about selecting artwork for the World Trade Center during the early 1970s. Files concerning Miller's advisory work with additional public and private clients, boards, and commissions are arranged in Series 7 and 8 and concern the Amstar Corporation, Fidelity International Bank, First National Bank of Tampa, First National City Bank (Citibank), Inmont Corporation, Pepsico, United Mutual Savings Bank, the Empire State Plaza Art Commission, the Hancock Shaker Village, the Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, the Mark Rothko Foundation, the Museum of American Folk Art, and the Smith College Museum of Art.
Miller's papers include a small group of files relating to the WPA Federal Art Project (FAP)created by her husband Holger Cahill when he was director of the FAP, Holger Cahill. A small series is devoted to Miller's work with Eleanore Price Mather researching and writing Edward Hicks: His Peaceable Kingdom and Other Paintings. A series of general research files contain miscellaneous research notes and photographs related to Miller's interests in early American art and folk art. Series 12 contains important documentation of Miller's early curatorial work with Holger Cahill on the First Municipal Art Exhibition (1934) held at the RCA Building in Rockefeller Center.
Works of art are primarily in the form of Christmas cards sent to Miller by various artists including Elise Asher, Lyonel Feininger, Bernard Karpel, and Irene Rice Pereira. A small group of photographs includes photographs of Miller from 1926-circa 1950 and a few photographs of others.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 14 series:
Series 1: General Biographical Material, 1917-1986 (Box 1; 0.3 linear ft.)
Series 2: Correspondence and Subject Files, circa 1912-1992 (Boxes 1-8, OV 27; 7.2 linear ft.)
Series 3: Rockefeller Family Art Collections, circa 1949-1985 (Boxes 8-12, 25; 3.9 linear ft.)
Series 4: Rockefeller University Collection, 1923-1984 (Boxes 12-13, OV 27; 1.0 linear ft.)
Series 5: Chase Manhattan Bank Collection, 1959-circa 1985 (Boxes 13-14, 26; 1.4 linear ft.)
Series 6: Port Authority of New York and New Jersey Art Committee, circa 1965-1987 (Boxes 14-15, OV 27; 0.8 linear ft.)
Series 7: Other Corporate and Private Clients, 1968-1984 (Boxes 15-16; 1.3 linear ft.)
Series 8: Other Boards, Committees and Commissions, 1925, 1949-1985 (Boxes 16-20; 3.6 linear ft.)
Series 9: Works Project Administration Federal Art Project Files, 1935-1979 (Box 20, OV 27; 0.5 linear ft.)
Series 10: Edward Hicks Catalog, 1934-1984 (Boxes 20-22; 1.5 linear ft.)
Series 11: Research Files, 1930s-1980 (Boxes 22-23; 0.8 linear ft.)
Series 12: Exhibition Files, 1932-1986 (Box 23; 0.6 linear ft.)
Series 13: Works of Art, circa 1924-circa 1982 (Boxes 23-25; 1.5 linear ft.)
Series 14: Photographs, 1926-circa 1970s (Boxes 24-25; 0.3 linear ft.)
Names and Subject Terms
This collection is indexed in the online catalog of the Archives of American Art under the following terms:
Subjects:
Hicks, Edward, 1780-1849; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979; Rothko, Mark, 1903-1970; Cahill, Holger, 1887-1960; Chase Manhattan Bank -- Art collections; Port Authority of New York and New Jersey -- Art collections; World Trade Center (New York, N.Y.) -- Art collections; Federal Art Project; Smith College -- Students; Municipal Art Exhibition (1st, 1934, New York, N.Y.)
Subjects-Topical:
Art, Modern -- 20th century; Art -- Private collections; Corporations -- Private collections; Art museum curators -- New York (State) -- New York; Art, Modern -- 20th century -- Exhibitions; Artists -- United States; Art historians -- New York (State) -- New York; Folk art
Types of Materials:
Christmas cards; Photographs; Drawings; Sketches
Names:
Copley, Alfred L.; Calder, Alexander, 1898-1976; Canady, John; Byars, James Lee; Barr, Alfred Hamilton, 1902-; Cahill, Holger, 1887-1960; Bontecou, Lee, 1931-; Christo, 1935-; Coggeshall, Calvert, 1907-1990; Feitelson, Lorser, 1898-1978; Gorky, Arshile, 1904-1948; Guggenheim, Peggy, 1898-; DeFeo, Jay, 1929-1989; Charlton, Maryette; Chryssa, 1933-; Davis, Stuart, 1892-1964; Noguchi, Isamu, 1904-1988; Nevelson, Louise, 1899-1988; Hartigan, Grace; Horwitt, Will; Newman, Barnett, 1905-1970; Matisse, Pierre, 1900-1989; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Johns, Jasper, 1930-; Levy, Julien; Picasso, Pablo, 1881-1973; Reinhardt, Ad, 1913-1967; Sheeler, Charles, 1883-1965; Still, Clyfford, 1904-; Rauschenberg, Robert, 1925-2008; Sterne, Hedda, 1910-; Scharf, William, 1927-; Sage, Kay; Karpel, Bernard, 1911-; Mather, Eleanore Price, 1910-; Pereira, I. Rice (Irene Rice), 1902-1971; Feininger, Lyonel, 1871-1956; Asher, Elise, 1914-; Rockefeller University; Betty Parsons Gallery; Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden; PepsiCo, inc.; Mark Rothko Foundation; Smith College. Museum of Art
Series Descriptions/Container Listing
- General Biographical Material, 1917-1986, Series 1:; (Box 1; 0.3 linear ft.)
  Scattered biographical materials primarily document Miller's education, awards, degrees, honors, and family history.
  - Awards and Honorary Degrees, 1917-1986, (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1947-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Christmas Lists, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Family History Notes and Item of Doll's Underwear, circa 1932, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Passport, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Printed Material About Miller, circa 1942-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Printed Material About Newark Museum Apprentice Class, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Record of Miller's Trip to Williamsburg, Virginia, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Rental Property Records, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Smith College Art Exams, 1923-1925 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Smith College Art History Notes, circa 1920s (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Smith College Commencement Books, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Smith College Miscellaneous Printed Material, circa 1925 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Smith College Report Card, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Smith College Yearbook, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Who's Who in American Art, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Correspondence and Subject Files, circa 1912-1992, Series 2:; (Boxes 1-8, OV 27; 7.2 linear ft.)
  This series contains Miller's personal and professional correspondence and subject files on individuals or subjects. Individual files may contain correspondence, photographs, printed materials, research notes, essays and other writings, and scattered artwork. There is correspondence with galleries, museums, art associations, artists and other individuals from the art world, including Alfred Barr, Alexander Calder, John Canaday, Chryssa, Grace Hartigan, Will Horwitt, Ray Johnson, Miller and Cahill family members, Louise Nevelson, William Scharf, Hedda Sterne, Clyfford Still, and many others. Correspondence includes sketches and drawings by Lewin Alcopley, Will Horwitt, Gaston Gerreaud, Ray Johnson, Fred Martin, and Robert Osborn. Files on Louise Nevelson include photographs of Miller and Nevelson, including ones taken at the dedication of Nevelson's sculpture at the World Trade Center in January 1979. The files on Chryssa contain photographs of the artist's studio.
  Files are arranged alphabetically by name or subject. For each letter of the alphabet, individually named files are followed by "Miscellaneous" files containing scattered correspondence with multiple correspondents.
  - Abash, Cecile, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Abbott, Berenice, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Abrams, Charles, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Abrams Original Editions, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Adolph and Esther Gottlieb Foundation, Inc., 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - African American Artists, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - African Art, circa 1950, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ahlander, Leslie Judd, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Alcopley, Lewin (Alfred L. Copley), 1955, 1960, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Aldrich Museum of Contemporary Art, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Alexander, C. Marie, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Allen, C. Edmonds, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Allentown Art Museum, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - American Art, 1961-1967 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - American Indians, 1976-circa 1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Andrews, Benny, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Andrews, Dorothy, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Antique Dealers, 1958-1974 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Archives of American Art, 1961-1982 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Artco, circa 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Arts Funding, 1969-1981 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Association of Professional Art Advisors, Inc., 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Association of the Bar, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Auctions, circa 1973-circa 1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Automobile Crashes, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - A, Miscellaneous: Abbott, Jere -- Avnet, Joan, 1966-1983 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Baizerman, Saul, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Baker, Mildred, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Ball, George, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Baltrusaites, Helene, circa 1965-circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Barr, Alfred, Margaret, and Victoria, 1967-1985 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    (includes photos of Alfred Barr's retirement)
  - Berkshire Museum Exhibition (1976), 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Best, Peggy Worthington, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Betty Parsons Gallery, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Biala, 1950-1980 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Biesel, Fred and Frances, circa 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Binning, Robin, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Bladen, Ronald, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Blank Postcards, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Blumenfeld, Jane (Holger Cahill's Daughter), 1960-1984, (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 57-58)
  - Bolotowsky, Ilya, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Bona, Ivo, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Bonino, Fernanda, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Bontecou, Lee, 1963-1982 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Boris, Bessie (Basha Klein), 1969-1987 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Boterf, Chester, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Botero, Fernando, 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Bourgeois, Louise, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Bowdoin College Museum of Art, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Bradshaw-Smith, Gillian, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Braman, Gladys, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Brett, Catherine: see Spencer, Niles and Catherine Brett (Box 1)
  - Brodie, Gandy, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Brody, Myron, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Bronowski, Jacob, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Brooks, James, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Brown, Jean, 1973-1981 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Burrage, Mildred, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Bush, Doris Proctor, 1968-1978 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Buxton, Mary (Mrs. Gordon Cain; Museum of Fine Arts, Houston), 1969-1976 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Byars, James Lee, 1969-1981 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - B, Miscellaneous (Box 2)
    - Bacon-Westlake, Alice -- Bartlett, Fred, 1963-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer -- Bertoia, Harry, 1974-1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Bhavasar, Natvar -- Briggs, Ernest, 1969-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Broida, Edward R. -- Bush, Jack, 1967-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cahill, Holger, circa 1934-1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Calder, Alexander, 1963-1982, (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 6-8)
    (includes photos of Miller, Calder and others)
  - Canaday, John, 1961-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Carpenter, Leonard, 1951-1978, (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  - Chace, Happy, 1973-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Charles Alan Company, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Charlton, Maryette, 1959-1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Childs, Bernard, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chirino, Martin, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Christmas Cards, circa 1938-circa 1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Chryssa, 1961-1989, (6 folders; see also OV 27) (Box 2, Folder 19-24)
  - Coggeshall, Calvert, circa 1955-circa 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Committee for the Visual Arts Inc., 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Cook, Howard and Barbara, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Copley, Alfred L.: see Alcopley, Lewin (Box 2)
  - Cornell, Joseph, 1961, 1972, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Currier Gallery of Art, 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 29)